Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - MCTP: Seminar Norm Fruchter, 30 Apr 2003; cuid1182; 2 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Women's Rights Conference, undated; cuid1183; 2 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - "From Fundemental Principles to Selection Criteria" Barbara Goldsmith Preservation Lecture Series, Hal Erickson, 24 Jun 2002; cuid1184; 2 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Jack Schwartz Retirement Dinner, 29 Oct 2004; cuid1185; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Securing America in the 21st Century, 9 Sep 2005; cuid1186; 4 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Courant Institute Interviews, 6 Oct 2005; cuid1187; 2 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - The End of Poverty, Jeffrey Sachs, 5 Oct 2005; cuid1188; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Luxury Dining, 20 Oct 2005; cuid1189; 2 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Gertrude Belle Elion, 11 Oct 2005; cuid1190; 2 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Jenny Holzer "For the City", undated; cuid1191; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Kimmel Opening Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1192; 1 Betacam (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies Alumni Panel, 14 May 2005; cuid1193; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Amy Goodman Lecture, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1194; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Food Writers of Greenwich Village, 10 Mar 2006; cuid1195; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Culture and Communications, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1196; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Visions of a Changing Theater, undated; cuid1197; 5 MiniDV (Box 74, Box 75)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1198; 10 DVCAM (Box 74, Box 75)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1199; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Simon Reynolds: Raw Footage, undated; cuid1200; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Downtown Show: Nightclubbing, n.d.; cuid1201; 2 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - APA studies: Globalization and China Economic, 1 Sep 2006; cuid1202; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Neil Postman Symposium, undated; cuid1203; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - NYU Metro Regional Alumni Brooklyn Dodgers 1955, 15 Nov 2005; cuid1204; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 10 Apr 2005; cuid1205; 1 videocassettes (Box 74)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy, 16 Nov 2005; cuid1206; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show, 24 Oct 2005; cuid1207; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - The National Conference for Community and Justice, 9 Feb 2006; cuid1208; 5 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - MIAP The Moving Image: Texts as Iodes of Metadata, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1209; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Convocation in Honor of Gordon Brown and Alan, 14 Dec 2005; cuid1210; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Taking Journalism Seriously, 21 Apr 2006; cuid1211; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Dean's Day, 13 May 2006; cuid1212; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - NYC TVC Reel, undated; cuid1213; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1214; 4 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1215; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show 2005, cuid1216; 8 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Stern Panel Dicussion, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1217; 3 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Security in Ghana, undated; cuid1218; 3 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Raw Video: Downtown Show, 27 Jan 2006; cuid1219; 3 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - "Ultraviolet", 18 Apr 2006; cuid1220; 8 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Zukerman Forum 2006, 18 Apr 2006; cuid1221; 4 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - National Public Policy Forum Debate, 22 Apr 2006; cuid1222; 4 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - King Juan Carlos Center, 1 Dec 2005; cuid1223; 2 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Wagner Admissions Video, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1224; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Leo Barsanili and Lehman Lecture, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1225; 1 DVCAM (Box 74)
  - Promo "Cribs" PSA, 12 Sep 2002; cuid1226; 1 MiniDV (Box 74)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 1, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1227; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Season 3 Islam, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1228; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 5, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1229; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 7 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1230; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 9 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1231; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 10 Britain, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1232; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 12 France, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1233; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 14 United States, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1234; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 16 India, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1235; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 18 Japan, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1236; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008: Preliminary Rounds B-roll, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1237; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1238; 4 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1239; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1240; 1 DVD-R (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Panel, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1241; 1 DVD-R (Box 75)
  - Siemens Competition Program History, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1242; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Siemns Competition Awards Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1243; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - September 11: Our University Remembers, 11 Sep 2006; cuid1244; 5 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Robert Rosenblum Symposium, 14 Oct 2006; cuid1245; 3 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Al Gore: Policy Address on Climate Change, 18 Sep 2006; cuid1246; 6 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Spotlights: Ann Morning, Perry Halkitis, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1247; 5 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Corrections, 10 Dec 2005; cuid1248; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Promo, undated; cuid1249; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs: Ann Morning Rought Segments, undated; cuid1250; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Promo, 9 Apr 2009; cuid1251; 1 videocassettes (Box 75)
  - President of Cyprus, 18 Sep 2009; cuid1252; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Metro Tech Education Meeting, 17 Jul 2006; cuid1253; 2 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Who Makes Policy on Africa? Raw Footage and Master Tapes, 17 Apr 2006; cuid1254; 2 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; DV; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; cuid1255; 1 DVD-R (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1256; 2 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1257; 2 DVD-R (Box 75)
  - Civil Rights Symposium, 28 Oct 2006; cuid1258; 4 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Who's in Charge? Old Media, New Media, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1259; 3 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - SCPS Marketing: Naomi Levine, 30 Apr 2007; cuid1260; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Chat with Financiers: Ajit Jain, 7 May 2007; cuid1261; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Wagner Intersections: Leslie Stahl Discussion, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1262; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Social Entreprenuership in the 21st Century, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1263; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Expanding the Vision: Recovery as a New, undated; cuid1264; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: Opening Remarks, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1265; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: The Millenium Village, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1266; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Trade an Africa Culture: African Agriculture, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1267; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Ourspace: DIY Media and the Future of Democracy, 9 Nov 2006; cuid1268; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1269; 3 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1270; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - MIAP Speaker Series: How to Find Film and Videos, 22 Sep 2006; cuid1271; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1272; 4 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1273; 4 DVD-R (Box 75)
  - Raw Stock Footage: Snow in Washington Square Park, 7 Mar 2007; cuid1274; 1 MiniDV (Box 75)
  - Hope Not Hate, 8 Sep 2002; cuid1275; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Hip Hop Journalism, 26 Oct 2004; cuid1276; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Grossberg Lecture, undated; cuid1277; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Robert McChesney Lecture, 11 Nov 2004; cuid1278; 2 videocassettes (Box 77)
  - Ultraviolet, undated; cuid1279; 3 MiniDV (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Campus Flash: Adutumn Fest, Ticket Central, 1 Sep 2002; cuid1280; 3 MiniDV (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Zantee Hou Interview for IRHC, undated; cuid1281; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Presidential Debate, 1 Nov 2004; cuid1282; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Beyond the Sea Segement CF, 1 Sep 2004; cuid1283; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Hayden Talent Show, undated; cuid1284; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Teach In: Who is Next? "North Korea and Beyond", 1 Apr 2003; cuid1285; 5 MiniDV (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Lost in Translation: Rough Final Cut PSA, undated; cuid1286; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - NYU TV Coming up Slate 2002, cuid1287; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - New York University Cribs 2003, cuid1288; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - University Stock Footage, undated; cuid1289; 4 MiniDV (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Women Who Cook for a Living in New York and Why, 11 Jul 2006; cuid1290; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Diet & Nutrition: Counseling a Dental Office, 8 Sep 2001; cuid1291; 3 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - The Relationship of Health Promotion, 25 Oct 2001; cuid1292; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Real Estate, 24 Oct 2001; cuid1293; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Habib Kiote, 5 Oct 2001; cuid1294; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - HIPAA School of Social Work, 24 mar 2003; cuid1295; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Gloria Cahill Interview, 21 Sep 2005; cuid1296; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Max Orestein: Hurricane Katrina Photography, 1 Nov 2005; cuid1297; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Aviva Levine Interview, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1298; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Bronfman Center Katrina Panel, 14 Sep 2005; cuid1299; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Senior Class Council c/o 2006, 3 Nov 2005; cuid1300; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Applefest, undated; cuid1301; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - The Matador movie press kit and interviews, undated; cuid1302; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - The Matador Brosnan Interview, undated; cuid1303; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Presidential Welcome 2004 (NYU class of 2008), cuid1304; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - TVC B-Roll, undated; cuid1305; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - NYU-TV Channel 15 Movie Promos F02/S03, undated; cuid1306; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - "25th Hour" Movie Promo and NYU TV Promo, 15 Sep 2003; cuid1307; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Bobst Interviews and Stand-Ups, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1308; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Bobst Stand-Ups and Exteriors, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1309; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Bobst Steadicam, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1310; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington, 8 Apr 2003; cuid1311; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington and her Mother, 16 Apr 2003; cuid1312; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Bobst B-Roll, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1313; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Holiday Stress, 1 Dec 2002; cuid1314; 3 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Coles Writing, Center, and Bobst Archives Footage, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1315; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Lauren Acuna: New Channel 1, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1316; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - APA Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 25 Feb 2003; cuid1317; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - SWANK Motion Pictures Promo, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1318; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - NYU Channel 15 Movie Promo, 1 Nov 2002; cuid1319; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Cooking Series: David Kamp, 6 Oct 2002; cuid1320; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - NYU Journalism: Jimmy Breslin Lecture, 18 Sep 2002; cuid1321; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Tisch School of Arts International Student Film, 28 Oct 2003; cuid1322; 2 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Big Valentine's Fun Day, 1 Feb 2002; cuid1323; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - ABA Dialogue on Freedom Slate, 22 Oct 2002; cuid1324; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Vision Fest 2004, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1325; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Welcome to New York University, undated; cuid1326; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Logo Animations, undated; cuid1327; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Food Series: From Here to There, Food Chains, 19 Oct 2006; cuid1328; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Food Series: "What We Eat" by Marion Nestle, 4 May 2006; cuid1329; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - National Endowment for the Arts NEW 4, 15 Apr 2004; cuid1330; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - ITP Interactive Telecommunications Program, 13 May 2003; cuid1331; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - "Film School" IFC Docu-series Junket and Campus, 23 Aug 2004; cuid1332; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Christmas and Happy Holidays 2001 Promo, 9 Dec 2001; cuid1333; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - FBI Mon. Class Project 3, 1 Jan 2003; cuid1334; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Remarque Lecture: Mark Danner The Politics of the Forever War, 14 Nov 2006; cuid1335; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Stand-up Founder's Memorial, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1336; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Inside NYU: Historic NYU, Campus Tour, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1337; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Deutsches Haus, Ireland House, 27 Jul 2005; cuid1338; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Archives, Stand-ups, and more, 22 Jul 2005; cuid1339; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Marvin Taylor and the Fales Library, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1340; 1 MiniDV (Box 76)
  - Conjunctions 25th Anniversary Reading, 7 Dec 2006; cuid1341; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Tony Judt Lecture: "Disturbing the Peace", 4 Dec 2006; cuid1342; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Fales Food Series: "What's with all these books on food?", 12 Dec 2006; cuid1343; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Translating the World: Engaging Americans in International Journalism, 2 Feb 2007; cuid1344; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - MLK Celebration Week at NYU: A Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, 17 Jan 2007; cuid1345; 2 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Moving Archipelago: A Century of Writing Filipino America, 11 Nov 2007; cuid1346; 6 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Entering at One's Own Rish: Dennis Cooper and Transgressive Writing, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1347; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - US Senator Charles E. Schumer (D-NY) at NYU, 21 Feb 2007; cuid1348; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Sharing the Life of Lisa Ellen Goldberg Memorial, 25 Feb 2007; cuid1349; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1350; 6 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1351; 1 DVD-R (Box 76)
  - Artist's Circles: How do they work and what do they do?, 25 Jan 2007; cuid1352; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - NYU's Media Talk: The Literary Life and the Print Editor's changing role in the world of Web 2.0 with Mr. Carr, 20 Mar 2007; cuid1353; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Moving Beyond Rhetoric and Toward Solutions, 30 Jan 2007; cuid1354; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Public Health, 27 Feb 2007; cuid1355; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Library: Harry Frankfurt, 19 Mar 2007; cuid1356; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1357; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1358; 1 DVD-R (Box 76)
  - Courant Masters Orientation, 11 Jan 2007; cuid1359; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Fales lecture B-Roll "Up is Up, But so is Down", 26 Oct 2007; cuid1360; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Fales: Writing New York Talks from Gotham City, 17 Apr 2007; cuid1361; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Leonard N. Stern Schoiol of Business: Ashok Sani, 27 Mar 2007; cuid1362; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - After CBGB: Gender, Sexuality, and the Future of Subculture, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1363; 3 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - MIAP & ITP: A Talk with Archivist & Visual Designer, 23 Mar 2007; cuid1364; 2 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Cooking with Color, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1365; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Greg Albanis - Security Training for Commencement, 22 Mar 2007; cuid1366; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Gallatin Panel: Body Image, 29 Mar 2007; cuid1367; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Casa Italiana, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1368; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Downtown Gallery B-Roll, 6 Feb 2006; cuid1369; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Downtown Galley Grey Art Gallery Tour, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1370; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Downtown Show Art Clips for Grey Art Gallery, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1371; 2 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1372; 6 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1373; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Politics & Parnoia Opening and Panels, 31 Mar 2007; cuid1374; 6 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Building a Food Professional Pedigree: New Roads to Knowledge and Success, 14 Jun 2007; cuid1375; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr.Wanda, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1376; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Pedro Noguera, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1377; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Aretha Ball, 19 Jul 2007; cuid1378; 1 DVCAM (Box 76)
  - Stern: Credit Crunch and Subprime Markets, 5 Nov 2007; cuid1379; 2 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - College of Arts and Science Fall 2007, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1380; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Israel at 60, 9 Dec 2007; cuid1381; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - A/P/A YellowFace Interview, 8 Dec 2007; cuid1382; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Thirteen/WNET "Can We Disagree", 1 Jan 2008; cuid1383; 4 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Reynolds Social Entrepreneurship in the 21st Century, 30 Jan 2008; cuid1384; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - All Library Staff Meeting "Creating the 21st Century Library", 8 Jan 2008; cuid1385; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Presidential Representitives on Transportation Panel, 31 Jan 2008; cuid1387; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Hidgon Class, 7 Feb 2008; cuid1388; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - The Reality Show 2006, 25 Sept 2006; cuid1389; 8 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - NYDIS Clergical Summit, 1 Jun 2007; cuid1390; 4 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Town Hall Meeting, 16 Nov 2006; cuid1391; 3 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Shoot, 15 Sep 2006; cuid1392; 3 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Downtown Show at Grey Art Gallery, undated; cuid1393; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Philanthropy Interviews, Nov 2006; cuid1394; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - How to Strengthen Communities to Solve Tough Societal Problems, 24 Jan 2006; cuid1395; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - James Hanley and Susana Piscitiello, undated; cuid1396; 1 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Mock Solicitation Audit, 5 Apr 2007; cuid1397; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1398; 4 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1399; 2 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - MIAP Fall 2005 Speaker Series: A Mexican, 14 Oct 2005; cuid1400; 2 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting and Dinner Final Edit, 7 Jul 2003; cuid1401; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - NYU Show #2, undated; cuid1402; 1 Digital_Betacam (Box 77)
  - Conference on Our Design, 5 Jun 2004; cuid1403; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music: Year 1, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1404; 1 DVD-R (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Thomas Bornemann, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1405; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - New York University Ultraviolet Live 2008, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1406; 10 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1407; 5 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1408; 1 DVD-R (Box 77)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: An Evening with James Schamus, 12 Mar 2008; cuid1409; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Hidden Hunger, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1410; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - APA Food Series: Why are we Afraid of Food?, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1411; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Fales Food Series: The Power of the Pen, 13 Mar 2008; cuid1412; 2 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - NYU's Media Talk Series, 25 Mar 2008; cuid1413; 4 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Courant Oral History Project: Louis Nirenberg, 23 Feb 2007; cuid1414; 1 DVCAM (Box 77)
  - Human Resources, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1415; 2 MiniDV (Box 77)
  - Stern CFR Panel, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1416; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Fales Library: Dennis Cooper Reading and Panel, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1417; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - 2007 Albert Gallatin Lecture "Defending Rights Without Courts and Judges", 10 Dec 2007; cuid1418; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - The Invisible Cure: Africa, the West, and the Fight against AIDS", 4 Dec 2007; cuid1419; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Library Staff Meeting, 1 Jan 2008; cuid1420; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Central HR I-9 Training, 8 Jan 2008; cuid1421; 4 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - MLK Celebration Week: Marquee Event, 24 Jan 2008; cuid1422; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - New York Institute of Philosophy: Ronald Dworkin, 13 Nov 2007; cuid1423; 3 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1424; 2 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1425; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1426; 3 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Jonathan Lear, 17 Nov 2008; cuid1427; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - NYU Wagner Reynolds Speaker Series, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1428; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Conversations about America, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1429; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 13 Nov 2008; cuid1430; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - The Global Burden of a Chronic Disease: A Rising Epidemic, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1431; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Global Financial Crisis and Future Impact, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1432; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1433; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1434; 1 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Institute of Ancient World: Speaker Mario Savio, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1435; 3 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - APA Dumpling & Dynasty: Morning Panels, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1436; 11 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - Parents Day, 18 Oct 2008; cuid1437; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1438; 2 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1439; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - MTA Ravitch Hearings Session 1 & 2, 15 Sep 2008; cuid1440; 6 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Martha Wilson Documentation: Dilemmas, undated; cuid1441; 1 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Fales Food Series, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1442; 1 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Sword of Judith Conference, 18 Apr 2008; cuid1443; 6 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - SARI Economics Interview, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1444; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Stern CFR Panel #3, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1445; 3 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - American Cheeses by Clark Wolf at Fales, 3 Dec 2008; cuid1446; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - How Food and Food Writing have Changed, 20 Nov 2008; cuid1447; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Hemmerding T. Haynes, 4 Dec 2008; cuid1448; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Filming Science (Secrecy), 19 Nov 2008; cuid1449; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Siemans Science Competition 2008, 7 Dec 2008; cuid1450; 8 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - HR: HIPAA Training Videos at Benefits, 5 Dec 2008; cuid1451; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Global Public Health Event: Human Rights, 23 Jan 2009; cuid1452; 3 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Economics DRI Conference, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1453; 4 DVCAM
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1454; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1455; 2 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - Donor Interviews: Tammiment Library, 11 Dec 2008; cuid1456; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - What Would the Poor Say: Debates in Aid, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1457; 4 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Reynolds: Social Entrepreneurship Chuck D Series, 26 Jan 2009; cuid1458; 3 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 20091; cuid1459; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 2009; cuid1460; 2 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - MLK Marquee Event, 22 Jan 2009; cuid1461; 4 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Court Reform in China, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1462; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Jim Abramson, 10 Feb 2009; cuid1463; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Zuckerman Forum 2009 Sessions 1,2,3, 13 Feb 2009; cuid1464; 6 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - YNH Coming Up Slates, undated; cuid1465; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - Program Office: Big fun Day, undated; cuid1466; 1 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - University Wide Rooftop Shoot, undated; cuid1467; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - Ahecha Move B-Roll, undated; cuid1468; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - Exterior Campus Reel, 6 Jun 2002; cuid1469; 1 MiniDV (Box 80)
  - Staff Interview, 6 Jun 20021; cuid1470; 1 MiniDV (Box 78)
  - John Sexton Martin Luther King Jr. Address, undated; cuid1471; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - Recognizing and Responding to Students in Need, 23 Feb 2009; cuid1472; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1473; 2 DVD-R (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1474; 2 DVCAM (Box 78)